What if he didn't act alone?
The Murder of Nicole Brown Simpson is a thriller, drama,
crime film directed by Daniel Farrands.
In 1994 Nicole Brown Simpson and her friend Ronald Goldman were brutally murdered
in her Los Angeles home by whom most believe to be O.J Simpson.
But what role did Glen Rogers, also known as the
Casanova Killer play in their death?
Nicole Brown Simpson, played by Mena Suvari.
Glen Rogers, played by Nick Stahl.
Faye Resnick, played by Taryn Manning.
Kris Kardashian, played by Agnes Bruckner.
Wood Sprite, played by CC King.
Ron Goldman, played by Drew Roy.
The Murder of Nicole Brown Simpson is a 2019 American crime
thriller film directed by Daniel Farrands.
The film is loosely based on the murder of Nicole Brown Simpson, presenting a fictionalized version of
events in which Brown Simpson is murdered by serial killer Glen Edward Rogers,  and not by O.
Simpson, her ex-husband and the primary suspect in the case.
Though Mena Suvari's performance as Nicole Brown was
praised, the film was panned by critics.
The film explores themes of murder, los angeles, california,
house painter, wife murderer, masked killer.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.